A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16 FA288
Rockefeller Archive Center
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Statistical Monthly Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1940 (Box 14, Folder 149)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Statistical Monthly Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1940 (Box 14, Folder 150)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Strachey, St. Loe - Correspondence, 1927-1941 (Box 14, Folder 151)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Strachey, St. Loe - Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box 15, Folder 152)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Strachey, St. Loe - Correspondence (These Two Strange Years), 1939-1942 (Box 15, Folder 153)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Summaries - Statistical Data, 1931-1935 (Box 15, Folder 154)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Treasurer's Correspondence and Memoranda, 1931-1933 (Box 15, Folder 155)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - Villiers, Paul - Correspondence, 1935-1938 (Box 15, Folder 156)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1953 (Box 15, Folder 157)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1953 (Box 15, Folder 158)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1953 (Box 15, Folder 159)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1953 (Box 15, Folder 160)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1953 (Box 15, Folder 161)
- London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1953 (Box 15, Folder 162)
- London School of Economics - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1939 (Box 16, Folder 163)
- London School of Economics - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1939 (Box 16, Folder 164)
- London School of Economics - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1939 (Box 16, Folder 165)
- London School of Economics - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1939 (Box 16, Folder 166)
- London School of Economics - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1939 (Box 16, Folder 167)
- London School of Economics - Financial Data and Correspondence, 1931-1952 (Box 16, Folder 168)
- London School of Economics - Financial Data and Correspondence, 1931-1952 (Box 16, Folder 169)
- London School of Economics - Financial Data and Correspondence, 1931-1952 (Box 16, Folder 170)
- London School of Economics - Financial Data and Takeover Correspondence, 1938-1941 (Box 16, Folder 171)
- London School of Economics - Foreign Fellowships - Dutch (Correspondence), 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 172)
- London School of Economics - Foreign Fellowships - Miscellaneous (B-V), 1932-1947 (Box 16, Folder 173)
- London School of Economics - Mental Health Course - Annual Reports, 1931-1948 (Box 17, Folder 174)
- London School of Economics - Mental Health Course - Annual Reports, 1931-1948 (Box 17, Folder 175)
- London School of Economics - Mental Health Course - Annual Reports, 1931-1948 (Box 17, Folder 176)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Academic Sub-Committee, 1932-1938 (Box 17, Folder 177)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Consultative Committee, 1930-1939 (Box 17, Folder 178)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Consultative Committee, 1930-1939 (Box 17, Folder 179)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 180)
  Financial Sub-Committee - May 1943 Lecturers - May 18, 1931 Selection Committee - March 1943
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Practical Training Committee/Conference, 1931-1939 (Box 17, Folder 181)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Practical Training Committee/Conference, 1931-1939 (Box 17, Folder 182)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Selection Committee, 1931-1938 (Box 17, Folder 183)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Selection Committee, 1931-1938 (Box 17, Folder 184)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Supervisors' Discussion Group, 1933-1938 (Box 17, Folder 185)
- London School of Economics - Minutes - Supervisors' Discussion Group, 1933-1938 (Box 17, Folder 186)
- London School of Economics - Reports/Special Studies, 1934-1940 (Box 18, Folder 187)
- London School of Economics - Statistical Data Re: Students, 1929-1942 (Box 18, Folder 188)
- London School of Economics - Statistical Data Re: Students, 1929-1942 (Box 18, Folder 189)
- London School of Economics - Training Courses - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1928-1931 (Box 18, Folder 190)
- London School of Economics - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1952 (Box 18, Folder 191)
- London School of Economics - War Emergency Plans - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1952 (Box 18, Folder 192)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Addresses Before Gatherings, 1932-1934 (Box 18, Folder 193)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Amalgamation - Feversham Committee (Minutes), 1936-1937 (Box 18, Folder 194)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Amalgamation - General Correspondence, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 195)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Amalgamation - General Correspondence, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 196)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Amalgamation - General Correspondence, 1930-1942 (Box 18, Folder 197)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Appeal - British Council of Child Research (Correspondence), 1928-1931 (Box 18, Folder 198)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Appeal - Central Association for Mental Welfare, Inc. (Correspondence), 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 199)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Appeal - East London Guidance Clinic (Jewish Health Organization's Child Guidance Clinic) (Correspondence), 1926-1932 (Box 18, Folder 200)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Appeal - Institute of Medical Psychology (Correspondence), 1928-1938 (Box 19, Folder 201)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Appeal - Maudsley Hospital Clinic (Correspondence), February-March, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 202)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Appeal - Institute of Industrial Psychology (Correspondence), 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 203)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Appeals Department - Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 204)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Board Reports (Commonwealth Fund), 1932-1939 (Box 19, Folder 205)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Cambridge Unit - Report, November 30, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 206)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Committee Members, 1930-1938 (Box 19, Folder 207)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Courses in Psychological Medicine (Great Britain) - Correspondence, March-October, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 208)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - General Correspondence, 1927-1931 (Box 19, Folder 209)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - General Correspondence, 1927-1931 (Box 19, Folder 210)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - General Correspondence, 1927-1931 (Box 19, Folder 211)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Maudsley Hospital Clinic, 1931-1935 (Box 19, Folder 212)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - New York School of Social Work (Lee, Porter R.), 1927-1930 (Box 19, Folder 213)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - New York School of Social Work (Liebeskind, Maria), 1940-1945 (Box 19, Folder 214)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Butler, Kathleen), 1927-1928 (Box 19, Folder 215)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Craggs, Katherine), 1927-1928 (Box 19, Folder 216)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Crosse, Olive W.), 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 217)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Ewen, Mildred), 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 218)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Fairbairn, Nancy), 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 219)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Findlay, Ellen M.), 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 220)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Garrett, Marion), 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 221)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Horder, Hilda), 1927-1929 (Box 20, Folder 222)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Hunnybun, Noel), 1927-1929 (Box 20, Folder 223)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Lee, Elizabeth), 1930-1935 (Box 20, Folder 224)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Lilley, Dorothy), 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 225)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (McFie, Bernice S.), 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 226)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Program Plans for Fellows), April-August, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 227)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Program Plans for Fellows), April-August, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 228)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Robinson, Beatrice Howard), 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 229)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Robinson, Doris), 1927-1928 (Box 20, Folder 230)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Psychiatric Social Worker (Streatfield, Margaret B.), 1928-1929 (Box 20, Folder 231)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Fellowships - Requests for Fellowships (A-W), 1930-1941 (Box 20, Folder 232)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - General Correspondence (A-B), 1929-1947 (Box 20, Folder 233)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - General Correspondence (C), 1928-1948 (Box 20, Folder 234)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - General Correspondence (D-F), 1929-1950 (Box 21, Folder 235)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - General Correspondence (G-H), 1928-1949 (Box 21, Folder 236)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - General Correspondence (J-M), 1929-1947 (Box 21, Folder 237)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - General Correspondence (N-R), 1931-1948 (Box 21, Folder 238)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - General Correspondence (S-W), 1931-1949 (Box 21, Folder 239)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Investigational Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1939 (Box 21, Folder 240)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Investigational Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1939 (Box 21, Folder 241)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Investigational Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1939 (Box 21, Folder 242)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Investigational Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1939 (Box 21, Folder 243)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Investigational Reports and Memoranda, 1929-1939 (Box 21, Folder 244)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - MacKintosh, James - Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 21, Folder 245)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - MacKintosh, James - Correspondence, 1944-1950 (Box 22, Folder 246)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - MacKintosh, James - Diary-Trip to Sweden, March 1945 (Box 22, Folder 247)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - MacKintosh, James - Report-Trip to the United States, September 12, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 248)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Mapother, Edward - Correspondence, 1929-1940 (Box 22, Folder 249)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Memoranda, November 26, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 250)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Mental Health Emergency Committee (Box 22, Folder 251)
  Correspondence - December 14, 1938-July 17, 1945 Minutes and Reports - July 1, 1939-December 12, 1942
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Minutes - Provisional National Council for Mental Health, 1942-1944 (Box 22, Folder 252)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - General Correspondence, 1927-1929 (Box 22, Folder 253)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Miscellaneous Observers (B-D), 1929-1940 (Box 22, Folder 254)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Miscellaneous Observers (E-H), 1933-1941 (Box 22, Folder 255)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Miscellaneous Observers (J-M), 1928-1940 (Box 22, Folder 256)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Miscellaneous Observers (O-Y), 1927-1940 (Box 22, Folder 257)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Beach, Lucy and Edith V. Eckhard), 1927-1928 (Box 23, Folder 258)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Beach, Lucy and Edith V. Eckhard), 1927-1928 (Box 23, Folder 259)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Brown, Sybyl Clement), 1934-1935 (Box 23, Folder 260)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Buchan, G. F.), 1927-1929 (Box 23, Folder 261)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Buchan, G. F.), 1927-1929 (Box 23, Folder 262)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Clinic Staff-Moodie, Fildes and MacTaggart), 1927-1929 (Box 23, Folder 263)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Clinic Staff-Moodie, Fildes and MacTaggart), 1927-1929 (Box 23, Folder 264)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Creak, Mildred), 1932-1933 (Box 23, Folder 265)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Crosthwaite, Agnes A.), 1931-1934 (Box 23, Folder 266)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Crowley, Ralph), 1927-1928 (Box 23, Folder 267)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Darwin, Ruth), October-November, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 268)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Fairfield, Letitia), 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 269)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Fox, Evelyn), 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 270)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Fox, Evelyn), 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 271)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Fox, Evelyn), 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 272)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Galloway, Janet), 1934-1935 (Box 24, Folder 273)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Green, George H.), July-September, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 274)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Guthrie, Helen), July-November, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 275)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Hart, Bernard), April-October, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 276)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Hart, Bernard), April-October, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 277)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Hunnybun, Noel), June-December, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 278)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Hyslop, J. S.), October 15-29, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 279)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Lawrence, E. M.), 1928-1929 (Box 24, Folder 280)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Lucas, R. Evelyn), 1928-1929 (Box 24, Folder 281)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Milnes, Nora), June-September, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 282)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Moodie, William), July-October, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 283)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Morton, T. M.), May-December, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 284)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Norris, Arthur H.), April-August, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 285)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Posthuma, Margaret), 1928-1933 (Box 25, Folder 286)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Pringle, J. C./Hincks, W. E.), 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 287)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Rees, J. N.), July 8-11, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 288)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Salmon, Janet), 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 289)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Shrubsall, Frank C.), 1926-1929 (Box 25, Folder 290)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Spearman, Charles), 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 291)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Townsend, St. Clair), 1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 292)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Observer (Worsthorne, Priscilla), 1931-1932 (Box 25, Folder 293)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Study Visitor (Mapother, Edward), 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 294)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Study Visitors (Cosens, Marjorie and Warner, Marion), 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 295)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Trips - Study Visitors (Cosens, Marjorie and Warner, Marion), 1928-1931 (Box 26, Folder 296)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Visitors - Interviews, November-December, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 297)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Visitors - Reports, 1927-1929 (Box 26, Folder 298)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Observational Visitors - Reports, 1927-1929 (Box 26, Folder 299)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Sources of Information - Memoranda and Correspondence [Mildred C. Scoville], 1926-1927 (Box 26, Folder 300)
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Sources of Information - Reports (Box 26, Folder 301)
  Care Committee - 1926 London County Council - 1926 National Council for Mental Hygiene - 1928 and 1929
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Take-Over Material (Box 26, Folder 302)
  Child Guidance Council - December 2, 1935-November 23, 1938 London Child Guidance Clinic - September 21, 1933-November 22, 1938
- Program for Mental Hygiene in England - Treasurer's Correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 26, Folder 303)